[CHURCH ACTOR ONE:] Most Reverend Cauchon
the courtroom waits your grace
The theologians
and clerics are here for the case
[CAUCHON:]Ah gentlemen
you know our task in Rouen
We've not much time
and big ask from Paris, London, Rome
[FOLLOWERS:] Vive la Vierge Jeanne! Long live Supermaiden!
Vive la Pucelle! Our Savioress!
Vive la Vierge Jeanne! Long live Supermaiden!
[D'ESTIVET:] Listen to that clamor
of peasants in the street
A maid lifts up a banner
and they fall at her feet
[COURTROOM:] She is dangerous!
[FOLLOWERS:] Joan of Arc, Our Savioress!
[FOLLOWERS:] Tell us that you are
who we say that you are
[CHURCH ACTOR TWO:] The Maid is in the tower
she will appear in court
[CHURCH ACTOR THREE:] A rabble-rousing mission
we are tasked to abort
[COURTROOM:] She is dangerous!
[FOLLOWERS:] Joan of Arc,
Our Savioress!
[COURTROOM:] She is dangerous!
[CHURCH ACTOR TWO:] Your Excellency, she steps right outside our yard
[CHURCH ACTOR THREE:] Most Reverend Cauchon, let in her English vanguard
[CAUCHON:] No, wait!
We need a more lasting solution
to any presumed plebiscite
[D'ESTIVET:] What then to do about this Joan of Arc?
Peasant supermaid, heroine of fools.
[CHURCH ACTOR THREE:] No riots, no armies,
no credo, no sainting
[CAUCHON:] One thing I'll say —- this Joan's not that bad
[D'ESTIVET:] We dare not leave her to her own devices,
Her misguided armies will soon get out of hand.
[COURTROOM:] But how can we stop her?
Her glamour increases,
She’s capturing cities;
she's topping the trends.
[CAUCHON:] I see bad things arising
The crowd-crowned queen,
the Word Order would ban
I see blood and rebranding
Our jobs outsourced because of one girl
Blood and rebranding because of one girl
[COURTROOM:] Because, because, because of one girl
[CAUCHON:] Our elimination because of one girl
[COURTROOM:] Because, because, because of one
Cause of one, cause of one girl
[CHURCH ACTOR THREE:] What then to do about this Joan mania?
[D'ESTIVET:] Now how do we deal
with a shepherdess queen?
[CHURCH ACTOR TWO:] Where do we start
with a Maiden bigger
[CHURCH ACTOR THREE:] Than even Charles was
when Charles was still the VI-th?
[CAUCHON:] Fools, you have no perception!
The stakes we are gambling
are frighteningly high!
We must burn her completely,
Like Charles VI before her,
this Joan of Arc must die.
For the sake of our Mother,
Catholic Church, no relics.
[COURTROOM:] Must die, must burn, this Joan must burn.
[CAUCHON:] Like Charles before Charles, this Joan has to die.
[COURTROOM:] We must burn her completely, this Maiden must burn to thin dust!
She must burn completely,
no proof of her being to everlast!