[1429]
[FOLLOWERS:] Vive Jeanne!
Hey Jeanne, Jeanne, Vive Jeanne!
Hey Jeanne, Vive Jeanne!
Hey Joan, Joan
won't you lead us on?
Jeanne, Vive Jeanne!
Vive La Pucelle d'Orléans!
[CAUCHON:] Tell your followers to be silent
we foresee a threat quite violent
This common host
has much too boast
Tell these fans who sing your praise
that they are fools and out of phase
They're not on the course
the Church will likely endorse
[FOLLOWERS:] Vive Jeanne!
Hey Jeanne, Jeanne, Jeanne, Vive Jeanne!
Hey Jeanne, Vive Jeanne!
Hey Joan, Joan,
you're a Saint, or Saint-to-be!
Jeanne, Vive Jeanne!
Hey Maid of Orléans!
[JOAN:] Why squander your words rebuking my fans?
If you stop their tongues,
beware of their hands
If tongues and hands were stilled
The sky and land themselves
Would start to sing
[FOLLOWERS:] Vive Jeanne!
Hey Jeanne, Jeanne, Jeanne, Vive Jeanne!
Hey Jeanne, Vive Jeanne!
Hey Joan, Joan,
Won't you win for France?
Jeanne, Vive Jeanne, Hey Maid of Orléans!
[JOAN:] Sing me your hymns,
But not just for me, do sing.
Sing out for all France,
For you are blessed
There is not one here
Who cannot win a soul
The meek, the brave,
The toiling and the giving.
[FOLLOWERS:] Vive Jeanne!
Hey Jeanne, Jeanne, Jeanne, Vive Jeanne!
Hey Jeanne, Vive Jeanne!
Hey Joan, Joan,
won't you burn for me?
Jeanne, Vive Jeanne, Hey Maid of Orléans!
(ALL CHEERING)
[FOLLOWERS:] Joan! Joan! Joan! Joan!