[role of: KING CHARLES VII]
My mind is clearer now,
At last all too well
I can see
where France
will soon be.
If you strip away
the myth from the maid,
You will see where
we all soon will be.
Joan! You've started to believe
The things they say of you.
You really do believe
This voice of Saints is true. Oh!
And all the good you've done
Will soon get swept away.
You've begun to matter more
Than voices you obey.
Listen Joan, I don't like what I see.
All I ask is that you listen to me.
Et n'oubliez pas, je suis ton roi!
You have kindled their zeitgeist.
They think they've found another Christ.
And they'll hurt you
if they'll find they're wrong.
I remember when
ton histoire began.
No talk of saints then,
you were une paysanne.
Et crois-moi,
mon promotion pour toi
est non encore incinéré.
But every word you say today
Gets twisted 'round some other way.
And they'll hurt you
if they think you've lied.
Domrémy, your famous daughter
should have stayed une anonyme
Like her father tending sheep,
she'd have made good.
Fields, farms, and rural charms
would have suited Joan best.
She'd have caused no alarms;
nobody would be distressed.
Listen, Joan, do you care for our France?
Bestow to peace a diplomatic chance.
We are English-occupied;
Our logistics are under-supplied.
I am frightened by your clout.
Peasants are getting much too flout.
And they'll crush us if they win a war.
If they win any war...
Listen, Joan, to the warning I give.
Please know that I want us to convive.
But it's sad to see our bond
weakening with every city that you bomb.
All your followers are blind,
Too much sainthood on their minds.
It was beautiful, but now it's tense.
Yes, it's all gone dangerously tense.
Oh oh oh oh oh
Yes, it's all gone dangerous.
Listen, Joan, to the warning I give.
Please know that I want you to live.
Allons y,
But she won't listen to me...
Allons y!
She won't listen to me...