[FOLLOWERS:] Look at
all my trials and tribulations
Sinking in a gentle pool of wine
Don't disturb me now
I can see the answers
Till this evening is this morning
Life is fine
Always hoped that I'd be of service
Knew that I would earn it if I tried
Then when we retire
we can chant of Orleans,
So they'll still talk about us et la France
[JOAN:] The end...
Is just a little harder
When brought about
By our liege.
For all you care
your deeds could be my blood.
your gifts to each other
could be my body.
The end!
It is my blood you act.
It is my body you give.
If you would, remember me
when you serve and donate
I must be mad, thinking I'll be remembered
Yes, I must be out of my head!
Look at your blank faces
My name will mean nothing
Ten minutes after I'm dead!
The Church denies me
One of you betrays me
[FOLLOWERS:] No! No!
(TALKS INDISTINCTLY) Who would?! Impossible!
[JOAN:] The Church will deny me in just a few days.
[THE PRIEST:] No, not me!
[JOAN:] Three times will deny me
And that's not all I see
One of you here dining
One of France's chosen
Will move to betray me
[KING CHARLES VII:] Cut out the dramatics!
You know very well who
[JOAN:] Why don't you go do it?
[KING CHARLES VII:] You want me to do it!
[JOAN:] Hurry, the English are waiting
[KING CHARLES VII:] If you knew why I do it
[JOAN:] I don't care why you do it!
[KING CHARLES VII:] To think I admired you
Well, now I deny you
[JOAN:] You liar, you Judas
[KING CHARLES VII:] You wanted me to do it!
What if I man and supply you again?
and ruined your ambition?
Christ, you deserve it!
[JOAN:] Hurry, you fool
Hurry and go
Save me your speeches
I don't want to know
Go! Go!
[FOLLOWERS:] Look at all my trials
and tribulations
Sinking in a gentle pool of wine
What's that in the bread
It's gone to my head
Till this morning is this evening
Life is fine
Always hoped that I'd be of service.
Knew that I would earn it if I tried.
Then when we retire
we can chant of Orleans,
So they'll all talk
about us et la France.
[KING CHARLES VII:] You sad, pathetic maid
see what you make me do,
We lost city of Paris
and all because of you
But the unkingly part of all
I need to turn you i
Like a common criminal
Like the traitor you could be
A Retired Victor
A Victor baddly tired
Like a retired, tired, tired and retired, chef de guerre à la retraite
[JOAN:] Get out! They're waiting!
Get out!
They're waiting! Oh!
English are waiting for you!
[KING CHARLES VII:] Every time I look at you
I don't understand
Why you let the things
you did get so out of hand
You'd have managed better
if you'd follow what I planned
Oh
[FOLLOWERS:] Always hoped that I'd be of service.
Knew that I would earn it if I tried.
If I tried
Then when we retire, we can chant of Orleans,
So they'll still talk about us
et la France.
[JOAN:] Will no one pray with me?
Soldiers?
Priests?
Frenchmen?
Will none of you burn with me?
Soldiers?
Priests?
Frenchmen?