[JOAN:] I only wish to say,
If there’s a way,
Keep the flames away from me,
For I am weaker than this torment.
Feel it burn me,
I have changed.
Once I heard voices, clear and sparkling.
Then, I was chosen.
Now, I’m trapped and poisoned.
Listen, surely I've met
Heaven's expectations,
Fought one long year,
seemed like twenty.
Has Jesus asked as much
from any other soul?
But if I burn,
See my path through
and keep my standard true,
Let them mock me,
scorn me, chain me,
stake me to the flames.
I want to know,
I want to know, dear Jesus,
Want to know,
I want to know, good Jesus,
Want to see,
I want to see, dear Saints,
Why I must burn.
Will my name shine brighter
than it ever has before?
Will all the hearts I moved
beat same drum evermore?
I need to know,
I need to know, dear Jesus,
Need to know,
I need to know, good Jesus,
Need to see,
I need to see, dear Saints,
I need to see, good Saints,
If I am ash
what will then be my crown?
Need to know,
I need to know, dear Jesus,
I need to know,
I need to know, good Jesus,
I need to know, my God,
Why must I burn?
Oh,
why must I burn?
Can you tell me now
my dust won't be forgotten?
Show me just a fragment
of your grand celestial plane.
Show me there's a reason
for my toils and pain.
You've chosen me for grilling
and tasked Rouen for embers.
Alright,
I'll burn!
Oh oh oh Just
Just watch me burn!
See
See how I burn!
Oh oh oh oh
Yeah
See how I burn!
Back then I was chosen,
Now, I'm trapped and poisoned.
After all,
I've tried for one year,
seems like always.
Angel Michael, for The Throne,
your white standard I've flown
In Rouen's fiery dawn,
I'll burn for Christ,
alone.
Heaven, your purpose is vast,
But in you, my trust is cast.
I'll wear your garb,
accept my past.
Take me to your stake,
Rouen.
Burn me, light me,
End me.
Take me, now!
Before my heart gives up.