[CAUCHON:] We've been sitting on
the fence for far too long
[D'ESTIVET:] Why let her upset us?
Cauchon, let her be
All those imbeciles will see
She really doesn't matter
[CAUCHON:] Joan is important,
We've let her go her way before.
And while she starts the revolution
We theorize and chatter
[D'ESTIVET:] He's just another
scripture-thumping hack from Lorraine
[CAUCHON:] The difference is they call her a Saint
This difference frightens me!
What about the Church?
When they see a new Maid crowned,
Do you think they'll stand around
Cheering and applauding?
What about our cardinals?
If they see we've lost our nerve
Don't you think that they deserve
Something less challenging?
[D'ESTIVET:] But followers got what they want
They think so anyway
If she's what they want
Why take their toy away?
She's a craze
[CAUCHON:] Put yourself in my place
I can hardly step aside
Cannot let my hands be tied
I am canon law and order
What about our priesthood?
Don't you see that we could fall
If we are to last at all?
We cannot be divided
[D'ESTIVET:] Then say so to the Clerics
But don't rely on subtlety
Let English scare them or they won't see
[CAUCHON:] Then we are decided?
[D'ESTIVET:] Then we are decided.