[CHARLES VII:] Now if I help you,
it matters that you see
These sordid kind of things
are coming hard to me
It's taken me some time
to work out what to do
I weighed the whole thing out
before I came to you
I have no thought at all about my own reward
I really didn't come here of my own accord
Just don't say I'm
Damned for all time!
I came because I had to
I'm the one who saw
Joan can't control it like she did before
And furthermore
I know that Joan thinks so too
Joan wouldn't mind that I was here with you
I have no thought at all about my own reward
I really didn't come here of my own accord
Just don't say I'm
Damned for all time!
Burgundians, you're friends, worldly men and wise
Cauchon, my friend I know you sympathize
Why are we the prophets?
Why are we the ones?
We see the sad solution
Know what must be done
I have no thought at all about my own reward
I really didn't come here of my own accord
Just don't say I'm
Damned
For all time!
[BURGUNDIANS:] Cut the protesting
Forget the excuses
We want information
Get up off the floor
[CAUCHON:] We have the papers
We need to arrest her
You know her movements
We know the canon law
[BURGUNDIANS:] Your help in this matter
won't go unrewarded
[CAUCHON:] We'll pay you in silver cash on the nail
We just need to know
where the soldiers can find her
[BURGUNDIANS:] With no armies around her
Then we can't fail
[CHARLES VII:] I don't want your blood money
[CAUCHON:] That doesn't matter,
our expenses are good
[CHARLES VII:] I don't need your blood money
[BURGUNDIANS:] But you might as well take it
We think that you should
[CAUCHON:] Think of the things
you can do with that money
Choose any charity, give to the poor
We've noted your motives
We've noted your feelings
[CAUCHON:] This isn't blood money, it's a...
[BURGUNDIANS:] A fee.
[CAUCHON:] A fee, nothing more
[CHARLES VII:] On Tuesday morning
You'll find her where you want her
Far from her army
tired, locked out of gates
(MUMBLES)
of Compiégne
[BURGUNDIANS:] Well done Sire
Good old Charles
(AIRPLANE ENGINE ROARS)