[JOAN:] Sire,
must you betray me...
before I win Paris?
(FLY BUZZING)
[FOLLOWERS:] What's the buzz
Tell me what's happening
What's the buzz
What's happening?
Tell me what's a-happening
What's the buzz
Hang on, Joan
We're gonna fight for you
[JOAN:] Put away your sword
Don't you know that it's all over?
It was nice, but now it's gone
Why are you obsessed with fighting?
Stick to treaties from now on
(CROWD CHATTERING)
(TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
[FOLLOWERS:] Tell me, Joan,
how you feel tonight
Do you plan to put up a fight?
Do you feel that you've had the breaks?
What would you say were your big mistakes?
Do you think that you may retire?
Did you think you would get much higher?
How do you view your coming trial?
Have your men proved it's all worthwhile?
Come with us - don't be seditious
You'll just love Rouen's courthouse
You'll just love seeing Cauchon
You'll just burn in the marketplace
Come on, Joan, this is not like you
Let us know what you're gonna do
You know what your supporters feel
You'll escape in the final reel
Tell me, Joan, how you feel tonight
Do you plan to put up a fight?
Do you feel that you had the breaks?
What would you say were your big mistakes?
Come with us - don't be seditious
You'll just love Rouen's courthouse
You'll just love seeing Cauchon
You'll just burn in the market place
Now we have her, now we've got her
Now we have her now
We have got her now
[CAUCHON:] Jeanne, you must realize
The serious charges facing you
You say you hear voices of saints
in all your posts
Well, is it true?
That's what you say
You say that I hear
There you have it, gentlemen
What more evidence do we seek?
Charles, thank you for the Maid
Stay a while and you'll see it smoke!
[FOLLOWERS:] Now we have her, now we've got her
Now we have her, now we've got her
Take her to Rouen, take her to Rouen!