[JESUS:] Try not to get worried
Try not to turn onto
Problems that upset you
Don't you know everything's all right?
Yes, everything's fine
And we want you to sleep well tonight
Let the world turn without you tonight
If we try, we'll get by
so forget all about us tonight
[FOLLOWERS:] Everything's all right, yes
Everything's all right, yes
[JESUS:] Sleep and I shall soothe you
Calm you and anoint you
Myrrh for your hot forehead
Then you'll feel everything's all right
Yes, everything's fine
And it's cool and the ointment's sweet
For the fire in your head and feet
Close your eyes, close your eyes
Relax, think of light tonight
[FOLLOWERS:] Everything's all right, yes
Everything's all right, yes
[KING CHARLES VII:] Hey, Christ
Your fine ointment, brand-new and exquisite
Should have been saved for a king
Why has it been wasted?
We could have raised maybe
300 silver pieces or more
People who are important
People who are of might
They matter more than
a paysanne's skin!
[JESUS:] Try not to get worried
Try not to turn onto
Problems that upset you
[JESUS:] Don't you know everything's all right?
[FOLLOWERS:] All right, yes
Everything's all right, yes
[JOAN:] Surely you're not saying
We have been elected
To lead kings against their will?
There will be mad kings
always in power
Look at the good things you've got!
Think while you still have France
Move while you still rule France
You'll be lost and you'll be sad
without a kingdom.
[JESUS:] Sleep and I shall soothe you
Calm you and anoint you
Myrrh for your hot forehead
Then you'll feel everything's all right, yes
Everything's fine
And it's cool and the ointment's sweet
For the fire in your head and feet
Close your eyes
Close your eyes and relax
Think of light
Tonight
[FOLLOWERS:] Close your eyes, close your eyes and relax
Think of light
[JESUS:] Close your eyes, close your eyes and relax
[FOLLOWERS:] Everything's all right, yes
[FOLLOWERS:] Everything's a light, yes
Close your eyes, close your eyes and relax
Everything's all light, yes
Everything's PURE LIGHT, yes