(CHATTERING)
CHORUS:  Roll on up, old faire Rouen
Come on in, old faire Rouen
Sunday, here we go again
Live in me, old faire Rouen
Here you live, old faire Rouen
Here you breathe, old faire Rouen
While Joan's saga still survives
You at least are still alive
I got things you won't believe
Name your pleasure, I will sell
ALL:  I can fix your wildest needs
I got heaven, I got hell
CHORUS:  Roll on up for my price is down
Come on in for the best in town
Take your pick of the finest wine
Lay your bets on this bird of mine
What you see is what you get
No one's been disappointed yet
Don't be scared, give me a try
There is nothing you can't buy
CHORUS:  Name your price, I got everything
Hurry, it's all going fast
Borrow cash on the finest terms
Hurry now while stocks still last
(ALL CHATTERING)
Roll on up, old faire Rouen
Come on in, old faire Rouen
Sunday, here we go again
Live in me, old faire Rouen
Here you live, old faire Rouen
Here you breathe, old faire Rouen
While Joan's saga still survives
You at least are still alive
I got things you won't believe
Name your pleasure, I will sell
(WOMEN SCREAMING)
(SINGING)  My death place should be
A house of good deeds
-(CLAMORING)
-(WOMAN SCREAMS)
But you have made it
A den of thieves
Rouen, Rouen.
You grilled me through.
For how many centuries
Have you sold my ashes?
(SINGING)  My time
Is almost through
Little left to do
After all
I've tried for centuries
Almost 6
Seems like always
See my time, I can hardly stop
See my face, it is hardly fair
I believe you can make me whole
See my votes, I need much more
MAN:  See my likes, I have too few
Fix the press, for my campaign
I believe you can make me well
See my account, I'm a poor, poor man
ALL:  Will you touch,
will you mend me, Joan?
Won't you touch, will you heal me, Joan?
Will you kiss, you can cure me, Joan
Won't you give, won't you pay me, Joan?
See my time, I can hardly stop
See my face, it is hardly fair
I believe you can make me whole
See my votes, I need much more
See my belly, I'm too fat
See my legs, I can hardly stand
I believe you can give me luck
See my account, I'm a poor, poor man
Will you touch, will you heal me, Joan?
Won't you touch, will you cuddle me, Joan?
Will you kiss, you can like me, Joan
Won't you give, won't you pay me, Joan?
See my time, I can hardly stop
See my face, it is hardly fair
I believe you can make me whole
See my votes, I need much more
See my belly, I'm too fat
See my time, I can hardly stop
I believe you can give me luck
See my account, I'm a poor, poor man
Will you touch, will you mend me, Joan?
Won't you touch, will you heal me, Joan?
Will you kiss, you can heal me, Joan
Won't you give, won't you pay me, Joan?
See my time, I can hardly stop
See my face, it is hardly fair
I believe you can give me luck
See my votes, I need much more
See my belly, I'm too fat
JOAN: There's too many of you!
I believe you can give me luck
JOAN: Don't push me!
Will you touch, will you mend me, Joan?
There's too little of me.
Will you kiss, you can like me, Joan
Don't crowd me!
See my time, I can hardly stop
Leave me alone!
See my votes, I need much more
MAN: Please, Joan!
WOMAN: Touch me, Joan!