[TODAY]
[JESUS CHRIST:] I've been waiting to see you.
You've been burning to see me,
but it shouldn't be like this.
You have over-performed,
Ready for Joan of Arc Romee, anew?
You are my only hope.
Papalis Infallibilitas too much.
Now for the first time,
I think The Pope was wrong.
Awake him ex cathedra,
Make his judgement pro tempore.
Joan, could we start la nouvelle guerre spirituelle?
[THE POPE:] I think you've made your point now.
You've even gone a bit too far to get the message home.
Before it gets too far,
We ought to call a vote,
Joan, could we start la nouvelle guerre spirituelle?
I've been waiting to see you.
You've been burning to see me,
but it shouldn't be like this.
You have over-performed,
Ready to be anew Joan of Arc Romee?
You are my only hope.
I think you've made your point now.
You've even gone a bit too far
to get the message home.
Before it gets too far,
We ought to call a vote,
Joan could we together start again la guerre?
Could we start la nouvelle guerre spirituelle? (1/5)
Could we start la nouvelle guerre spirituelle? (2/5)
Could we start la nouvelle guerre spirituelle? (3/5)
Could we start la nouvelle guerre spirituelle? (4/5)
[JESUS CHRIST:] Joan, could we start la nouvelle guerre spirituelle?