[TODAY]
[NAPOLEON:] Every time I look at you,
I don't understand
Why you let the things
you did get so out of hand
You'd have managed better
if I'd had you planned
Now why'd you choose
such a backward time in such a strange land?
If you'd come today
you could have reached the whole nation
France in 15th cent had no mass communication
[FOLLOWERS:] Don't you get me wrong
[NAPOLEON:] Don't you get me wrong
[FOLLOWERS:] Don't you get me wrong now
[FOLLOWERS:] Don't you get me wrong
[NAPOLEON:] Don't you get me wrong
[FOLLOWERS:] Don't you get me wrong now
[FOLLOWERS:] Only wanna know
[NAPOLEON:] Only wanna know
[FOLLOWERS:] Only wanna know now
[FOLLOWERS:] Only wanna know
[NAPOLEON:] Only wanna know
I only wanna know
[FOLLOWERS:] Joan of Arc
Joan of Arc
Who are you?
Why were you sacrificed?
Joan of Arc
Who are you?
Why were you sacrificed?
Joan of Arc
SuperMaid
Do you think you're what we say you are?
Joan of Arc
SuperMaiden
Do you think you're what we say you are?
[NAPOLEON:] Tell me
What you think about your friends at the top
Now who'd you think besides yourself
was the pick of the crop?
Buddha, was he where it's at?
Is he where you are?
Was Jesus truly Christ,
or was his mind subpar?
Did you mean to burn like that?
Was that a mistake,
Or did you know your story
would spawn record fakers?
[FOLLOWERS:] Don't you get me wrong
[NAPOLEON:] Don't you get me wrong
[FOLLOWERS:] Don't you get me wrong now
[FOLLOWERS:] Don't you get me wrong
[NAPOLEON:] Don't you get me wrong
[FOLLOWERS:] Don't you get me wrong now
[FOLLOWERS:] Only wanna know
[NAPOLEON:] Only wanna know
[FOLLOWERS:] Only wanna know now
[FOLLOWERS:] Only wanna know
[NAPOLEON:] Only wanna know
[FOLLOWERS:] Only wanna know now
I only wanna know
Joan of Arc
Who are you?
Why were you sacrificed?
Joan of Arc
Who are you?
Why were you sacrificed?
[FOLLOWERS:] Joan of Arc, SuperMaid
[NAPOLEON:] Jeanne
[FOLLOWERS:] I only wanna know
[NAPOLEON:] Do you think you're what they say you are?
[FOLLOWERS:] Tell me, tell me, tell me, tell me
[NAPOLEON:] Joan of Arc, SuperMaid
Don't you get me wrong
I only wanna know
[FOLLOWERS:] Joan of Arc, I only wanna know
Jeanne
I only wanna know
[FOLLOWERS:] Joan of Arc, I only wanna know
[NAPOLEON:] Tell me, tell me, tell me, tell me
[FOLLOWERS:] Tell me, tell me
[NAPOLEON:] Don't you get me wrong
I only wanna know
Come on
[FOLLOWERS:] Jeanne
[NAPOLEON:] Jeanne
Jeanne
[FOLLOWERS:] Only wanna know, Jeanne
[FOLLOWERS:] Only wanna know
[NAPOLEON:] I only wanna know
[NAPOLEON:] Tell me, tell me, tell me, tell me
Joan of Arc, SuperMaid
Don't you get me wrong,
I only wanna know
[NAPOLEON:] Come on, Jeanne
[FOLLOWERS:] Joan of Arc
Jeanne
I only wanna know
Tell me
Tell me, tell me, tell me