[KING CHARLES VII:] It seems to me a strange thing
Mystifying
That a Christ like you bestows his light
On a lowly paysanne like her
[LA HIRE] Hey, cool it, king.
[KING CHARLES VII:] Yes, I can understand that
She is a hero
But to let her hear you and your saints
That's hardly in your line
It's not that I object to her toils
But she doesn't fit in well
with what your Church teaches
It doesn't help us if the Church is inconsistent
The English only need a small excuse
To make all world theirs
[JESUS CHRIST:] Who are you to criticize her?
Who are you to despise her?
Leave her, leave her
Let her be now
She's with me now
If your slate is clean
then you can throw stones
If your slate is not, then leave her alone!
[FOLLOWERS:] Hey, Jesus, what do we say?
-Hey, Jesus, what do we say?
-(CLAMORING)
[JESUS CHRIST:] I'm amazed that you influencers
Can be so shallow, thick and slow
There is not a soul among you
who knows or cares where I come or go
[FOLLOWERS:] No, you're wrong
You're very wrong
No, you're wrong
How can you say that?
[JESUS CHRIST:] Not one.
[JESUS CHRIST:] Not one of you!