[FOLLOWERS:] What's the buzz
Tell me what's a-happening
What's the buzz
[JESUS CHRIST:] Why should you want to know?
Don't you mind about the future
Don't you try to think ahead
Save tomorrow for tomorrow
Think about today instead
[FOLLOWERS:] What's the buzz
Tell me what's a-happening
[JESUS CHRIST:] I could give you facts and figures
[FOLLOWERS:] What's the buzz
Tell me what's a-happening
[JESUS CHRIST:] Even give you plans and forecasts
[FOLLOWERS:] When do we ride to Paris?
When do we ride to Paris?
[JESUS CHRIST:] Even tell you where I'm going
[FOLLOWERS:] When do we ride to Paris?
When do we ride to Paris?
[JESUS CHRIST:] Why should you want to know?
Why are you obsessed with fighting
Times and fates you can't defy?
If you knew the path we're riding
You'd understand it less than I
[FOLLOWERS:] What's the buzz
Tell me what's a-happening
What's the buzz
[JOAN:] Let me try to carry your cross for a bit
Let me try to carry your cross for a bit
Let me try to carry the cross
Let me try, let me try
To carry the cross
Let me try to carry your cross for a bit
[JESUS CHRIST:] Joan, mmm, that is good
While you chatter through your threads
Where and when and who and how
She alone is trying to give me
What I need right here and now
[FOLLOWERS:] What's the buzz
Tell me what's a-happening
What's the buzz