[NAPOLEON:] Who is
This ghostly maid
appearing
in my presence?
Who is this spectral form?
[FOLLOWER:] It's Joan of Arc,
Queen of France.
[NAPOLEON:] Ah.
So this is Joan of Arc.
I've read about your spark.
You look so small.
Unfit for a war.
I've heard your tale of woes,
But are you she?
The Armored Savioress?
[JOAN:] Your words, not mine.
[NAPOLEON:] What do
you mean by that?
That is not proper reply
Je suis l'Empereur
du Monde, shepherd
Called Queen of the French
How can someone in your state
Be so cool about her fate?
Perplexing circumstance,
this silent queen of France.
Since you fought for The Cross
I am surely not your boss
You're Church's face!
(SMIRKS)
You're Pope's case!
[FOLLOWERS:] Hey Joan, Hey Joan
Joan of Arc
Hey Joan, brave heart
your spark will start
please make it clear
You led men before,
Why are you here?