Joan,
I am extatic...
(SINGING)  To meet you face-to-face
You got signs of sainthood
all around your case
-Leading armies
-Ooh.
Hearing voices from on-high
(ALL GASP)
And some claim you're God-sent
-(GASPS)
-Mmm.
-Huh?
THE POPE: (SINGING)
that I must canonize.
So
So, you are the Maid
you're the Church's SuperMaid
Operate the change of fate;
anoint yourself a saint
Perform this small feat
make all skeptics retreat
Come on, Supermaiden
Joan, you can't conceive
the stir you've made in Rome
You're on everyone's lips,
from pauper to the dome
Oh
What a tale if it turns out false, my dear
But I believe
you could sway the critics, have no fear
So, you are the Maid,
you're Church's SuperMaid.
Show to me you're Heaven's tool;
walk unburned through fiery fuel
-If you pass through the flame,
-CROWD: Whoo!
-holy I will make your name
Come on, Maid of Orléans
I ask you as I would of any saint-to-be
What gift from God was placed on you
where all the world can see?
Oh-oh-oh
I am waiting
as the Church's guiding hand
Awaiting proof that you're apart
from those in the normy band
So, if you are the Maid
the proclaimed Saint Joan
Fill the github with your deeds
heal world hunger and all needs
Or are tales all gone wrong?
Joan, why make us wait so long?
Oh! Come on, you Supermaiden
(SINGING)  Hey! Doesn't
Church Triumphant scare you, Joan?
Oh, Venerable Joan of Arc?
You're a trademark, not a saint.
Proof is what we want, not quaint.
(SINGS)  Keep her away,
Next audience: next century!
Speak no more, Joan of,
Silence, Joan of,
Quiet, you Venerable Blessed Saint Joan of Arc!
THE POPE: Leave our records!
Your standard leads nowhere, Joan,
Erase her from our archives!