[NAPOLEON:] And so the Queen
Is once again my guest
And why is this?
Was The Pope unimpressed?
[CAUCHON:] We turn to history
To seal our judgement
We have no way
To pain her after death
We need her totally forgotten
It's all you have to do
We need her erased from history
[NAPOLEON:] Talk to me, Joan of Arc
You have been brought here
Manacled, burned, by your own people.
Do you have the first idea
why you deserved it?
[NAPOLEON:] Listen Savioress of France,
Where are your saved?
Look at me
Am I saved?
[JOAN:] I have no savings
In the world, I'm through.
[FOLLOWERS:] Talk to me, Joan of Arc
[JOAN:] There may be something saved for me somewhere.
If you only knew.
[NAPOLEON:] Then you are a savioress?
[JOAN:] It's you who say I am
I look for truth and find that I get grilled
[NAPOLEON:] And what is truth?
Is truth unchanging law?
We both have truths
Are mine the same as yours?
[FOLLOWERS:] Forget of her! Erase her deeds!
[NAPOLEON:] What do you mean? You'd forget your savioress?
[FOLLOWERS:] We have no savior but our own selves!
[NAPOLEON:] She's done no wrong.
No, not the slightest thing.
[FOLLOWERS:] We have no savior but our own selves!
Erase her!
[NAPOLEON:] What is this new respect for self?
This looks imported from New Orleans.
Who is this Saint? Why is she different?
You choose bad leaders by the sackful.
[FOLLOWERS:] We need her edited out,
It's all you have to do
We need her erased,
[NAPOLEON:] Talk to me, Joan of Arc
Look at your Joan of Arc
I'll agree she's mad
Ought to be re-trialed
But that is not a reason to erase her
She's a sad, little girl, not a Savior or Christ
Not even a liar, I need a crime!
[FOLLOWERS:] Erase her! Erase her!
(CLAMORING)
Erase her! Erase her!
[NAPOLEON:] Behold a Maiden,
behold your shattered Queen
[FOLLOWERS:] We have no saviour but US!
[NAPOLEON:] You hypocrites,
you hate US more than her
[FOLLOWERS:] We have no king but US!
Erase her!
[NAPOLEON:] I see no reason, I find no evil
This girl is harmless
so why does she upset you?
She's just misguided, thinks she's important
But to keep you vultures happy,
I shall edit her!
[FOLLOWERS:] Erase her! Erase her!
Erase! Erase!
Erase her! Erase her!
[NAPOLEON:] One,
(YELLS)
two,
three,
four,
five,
six,
seven,
eight,
nine,
(PANTS)
(PANTING)
[NAPOLEON:] Where are you from, Jeanne?
What do you want, Jeanne?
Tell me
You've got to be careful
You could be erased soon
Could well be
Why do you not speak
When I hold your history in my hands?
How can you stay quiet?
I don't believe you understand
[JOAN:] You have no power in your hands
Any power you have
comes to you from far beyond.
Everything is fixed, and you can't change it.
[NAPOLEON:] You're a fool, Joan of Arc!
How can I help you?
[FOLLOWERS:] Napoleon, erase her! Erase!
For all posterity
You have a duty to document French virtues
So, erase her!
For all posterity
You'll be demoted, you'll be deported
Erase her!
For all posterity
You have a duty to document French virtue
So erase her!
For all posterity
You'll be demoted, you'll be deported
Erase her!
For all posterity
You have a duty to document French virtue
So erase her!
For all posterity
You'll be demoted, you'll be deported
Erase her!
[NAPOLEON:] Don't let me stop
Your great self-destruction
Be forgotten if you want to
You misguided martyr!
I wash my hands
Of your demolition
Be forgotten if you want to
You innocent soul!