[JESUS CHRIST:] Close your eyes, close your eyes
Look up into
The Light
I know how to lead her.
What to do
How to move her
She's been changed
Yes, really changed
In these past few hundred years
since she is here,
She seems like someone else.
I don't know how to take this
I can see why she moves me
She's a girl
She's just a girl
And I've led so many girl souls before,
In very many ways
She's just one more
Should I bring her down
Should I rise her up?
Should I speak of might
Let my Heavens light?
I bent light come into her
Will she see it inside?
Don't ya think it's rather funny
I should be in this position?
I'm the one
Who's always been
So calm, so cool
A model of God's tool
Running the ageless show
She loves me so
I feel her true
Now she's anew
Her scars erased
Her mission rebased
Now she will see
What she was meant
To be
What her burning
Meant for me
In my eternity
In God's eternity
She trusts me so
I know her so
I guide her
Soul