[roles of: La Hire, Mercenaries]
[MERCENARIES:]
Joan, you know I love you.
Did you see my grin?
I believe in you and Christ,
So lead me to a win.
Joan, you know I love you.
Did you see my grin?
I believe in you and Christ,
So lead me to a win.
Joan, I am with you.
Guide me, guide me, Joan.
Joan, I fight for you.
Lead me, lead me, Joan.
[LA HIRE:]
Joan, what more do you need to convince you,
That you're our Leader and easily as strong
As the English who plunder our homeland,
And who've terrorized the Frenchmen for so long.
[MERCENARIES:]
Joan, I am with you.
Guide me, guide me, Joan.
Joan, I fight for you.
Lead me, lead me, Joan.
Joan, you know I love you.
Did you see my grin?
I believe in you and Christ,
So lead me to a win.
Joan, I am with you.
Guide me, guide me, Joan.
Joan, I fight for you.
Lead me, lead me, Joan.
[LA HIRE:]
There must be legions upon legions
Screaming love and blood for you.
[MERCENARIES:]
Love! Love! Blood! Love!
[LA HIRE:]
And every man of all these legions
Would do whatever you ask him to.
[MERCENARIES:]
Anything you ask me to!
[LA HIRE:]
Keep them yelling their devotion,
But add a touch of hate of English band.
You will rise a greater standard,
We will win ourselves a land.
You'll get the might and the light
For ever and ever and ever
You'll get the might and light,
you'll get to be a saint
For ever and ever and ever
Forever Amen! Amen! Amen!