[FOLLOWERS:] I think I've seen you somewhere
I remember.
You were with that maid they took away
I recognize your face
[CHURCHMAN:] You've got the wrong man, people
I don't know her
And I wasn't where she was
Never near the place
[FOLLOWERS:] That's strange for I am sure
I saw you with her
You were right by her side
and yet you denied
[CHURCHMAN:] I tell you, I was never, ever with her
[FOLLOWERS:] But I saw you, too. He looked just like you.
[CHURCHMAN:] I don't know that Maid!
[JESUS CHRIST:] Churchman,
Don't you know what you have said?
You've gone and cut Christ dead
[CHURCHMAN:] I had to do it
Don't you see?
Or else they'd go for me
[JESUS CHRIST:] It's what she told you
you would do
Do you wonder
how she knew?