[FOLLOWER:] My God, I saw her
she looked three-quarters dead
and she was so bad, I had to turn my head
You poisoned her
and she was almost broken
And I know who everybody's gonna blame
I don't believe she knows I acted for our good
I'd save her all this suffering if I could
Don't believe our good
And I'd save her if I could
[POLITICIANS:] Cut the confessions, forget the excuses
I don't understand why
you're filled with remorse
All that you've said
has come true with a vengeance
Her followers turned against her
You backed the right horse
What you have done
will be the saving of everyone
You'll be remembered forever for this
And not only that
You've been paid for your efforts
Pretty good wages for one little girl
[FOLLOWER:] Joan, I know you can't hear me
But I only did what your mission needed me to
Joan, I'd sell out the nation
For I have been saddled
with the murder of you
I have been spattered with innocent blood
I shall be dragged
through the slime and the mud
I have been spattered with innocent blood
I shall be dragged
through the slime and the slime and the
Slime and the mud
I
Don't know how to thank her
I don't know why she made me lead
She's a girl
She's just a girl
She is not a Christ
She's just the same
As any other celebrity
She scares me so
While she's scattered ashes
Will she let me free?
Will she forgive
Will she forgive me too?
Does she still care for her Followers?
My mind is
It's in darkness
God.
God, I'm sick!
I've been used!
And you knew all the time!
God! God, I will never know
why you chose me
for your crime!
For your bloody crime!
You have crowned me!
Crowned me!
Crowned me! Elevated me!
Crowned me, Joan!
[FOLLOWERS:] So long, Follower
Poor old Follower
So long, Follower