[Good.]
The lyrics will appear here (at he right time, not now)
[1805]
[NAPOLEON:] I dreamed I met a maid from France
A most inspiring soul
She had that look
You seldom see
The fearless, yet restrained
I asked her
what compelled her be
How her story begun
I questioned her
she said no word
As if in other world
And next
The room was full
of stern and armored men
They seemed in awe of her
They knelt and then
They vanished once again
Then I saw
Then I saw legions upon legions
Cheering for this one maid
And then I heard them
chant my name
As if our fates
were braid
[FOLLOWERS:]  Vive l'Empereur!
[THE POPE:]  Vivat imperator in aeternum!
[1429]
[FOLLOWERS:] Vive Jeanne!
Hey Jeanne, Jeanne, Vive Jeanne!
Hey Jeanne, Vive Jeanne!
Hey Joan, Joan
won't you lead us on?
Jeanne, Vive Jeanne!
Vive La Pucelle d'Orléans!
[CAUCHON:] Tell your followers to be silent
we foresee a threat quite violent
This common host
has much too boast
Tell these fans who sing your praise
that they are fools and out of phase
They're not on the course
the Church will likely endorse
[FOLLOWERS:] Vive Jeanne!
Hey Jeanne, Jeanne, Jeanne, Vive Jeanne!
Hey Jeanne, Vive Jeanne!
Hey Joan, Joan,
you're a Saint, or Saint-to-be!
Jeanne, Vive Jeanne!
Hey Maid of Orléans!
[JOAN:] Why squander your words rebuking my fans?
If you stop their tongues,
beware of their hands
If tongues and hands were stilled
The sky and land themselves
Would start to sing
[FOLLOWERS:] Vive Jeanne!
Hey Jeanne, Jeanne, Jeanne, Vive Jeanne!
Hey Jeanne, Vive Jeanne!
Hey Joan, Joan,
Won't you win for France?
Jeanne, Vive Jeanne, Hey Maid of Orléans!
[JOAN:] Sing me your hymns,
But not just for me, do sing.
Sing out for all France,
For you are blessed
There is not one here
Who cannot win a soul
The meek, the brave,
The toiling and the giving.
[FOLLOWERS:] Vive Jeanne!
Hey Jeanne, Jeanne, Jeanne, Vive Jeanne!
Hey Jeanne, Vive Jeanne!
Hey Joan, Joan,
won't you burn for me?
Jeanne, Vive Jeanne, Hey Maid of Orléans!
(ALL CHEERING)
[FOLLOWERS:] Joan! Joan! Joan! Joan!
[KING CHARLES VII:]
My mind is clearer now,
At last all too well
I can see
where France
will soon be.
If you strip away
the myth from the maid,
You will see where
we all soon will be.
Joan! You've started to believe
The things they say of you.
You really do believe
This voice of Saints is true. Oh!
And all the good you've done
Will soon get swept away.
You've begun to matter more
Than voices you obey.
Listen Joan, I don't like what I see.
All I ask is that you listen to me.
Et n'oubliez pas, je suis ton roi!
You have kindled their zeitgeist.
They think they've found another Christ.
And they'll hurt you
if they'll find they're wrong.
I remember when
ton histoire began.
No talk of saints then,
you were une paysanne.
Et crois-moi,
mon promotion pour toi
est non encore incinéré.
But every word you say today
Gets twisted 'round some other way.
And they'll hurt you
if they think you've lied.
Domrémy, your famous daughter
should have stayed une anonyme
Like her father tending sheep,
she'd have made good.
Fields, farms, and rural charms
would have suited Joan best.
She'd have caused no alarms;
nobody would be distressed.
Listen, Joan, do you care for our France?
Bestow to peace a diplomatic chance.
We are English-occupied;
Our logistics are under-supplied.
I am frightened by your clout.
Peasants are getting much too flout.
And they'll crush us if they win a war.
If they win any war...
Listen, Joan, to the warning I give.
Please know that I want us to convive.
But it's sad to see our bond
weakening with every city that you bomb.
All your followers are blind,
Too much sainthood on their minds.
It was beautiful, but now it's tense.
Yes, it's all gone dangerously tense.
Oh oh oh oh oh
Yes, it's all gone dangerous.
Listen, Joan, to the warning I give.
Please know that I want you to live.
Allons y,
But she won't listen to me...
Allons y!
She won't listen to me...
[FOLLOWERS:] Look at
all my trials and tribulations
Sinking in a gentle pool of wine
Don't disturb me now
I can see the answers
Till this evening is this morning
Life is fine
Always hoped that I'd be of service
Knew that I would earn it if I tried
Then when we retire
we can chant of Orléans,
So they'll still talk about us et la France
[JOAN:] The end...
Is just a little harder
When brought about
By our liege.
For all you care
your deeds could be my blood.
your gifts to each other
could be my body.
The end!
It is my blood you act.
It is my body you give.
If you would, remember me
when you serve and donate
I must be mad, thinking I'll be remembered
Yes, I must be out of my head!
Look at your blank faces
My name will mean nothing
Ten minutes after I'm dead!
The Church denies me
One of you betrays me
[FOLLOWERS:] No! No!
(TALKS INDISTINCTLY) Who would?! Impossible!
[JOAN:] The Church will deny me in just a few days.
[THE PRIEST:] No, not me!
[JOAN:] Three times will deny me
And that's not all I see
One of you here dining
One of France's chosen
Will move to betray me
[KING CHARLES VII:] Cut out the dramatics!
You know very well who
[JOAN:] Why don't you go do it?
[KING CHARLES VII:] You want me to do it!
[JOAN:] Hurry, the English are waiting
[KING CHARLES VII:] If you knew why I do it
[JOAN:] I don't care why you do it!
[KING CHARLES VII:] To think I admired you
Well, now I deny you
[JOAN:] You liar, you Judas
[KING CHARLES VII:] You wanted me to do it!
What if I man and supply you again?
and ruined your ambition?
Christ, you deserve it!
[JOAN:] Hurry, you fool
Hurry and go
Save me your speeches
I don't want to know
Go! Go!
[FOLLOWERS:] Look at all my trials
and tribulations
Sinking in a gentle pool of wine
What's that in the bread
It's gone to my head
Till this morning is this evening
Life is fine
Always hoped that I'd be of service.
Knew that I would earn it if I tried.
Then when we retire
we can chant of Orléans,
So they'll all talk
about us et la France.
[KING CHARLES VII:] You sad, pathetic maid
see what you make me do,
We lost city of Paris
and all because of you
But the unkingly part of all
I need to turn you i
Like a common criminal
Like the traitor you could be
A Retired Victor
A Victor baddly tired
Like a retired, tired, tired and retired, chef de guerre à la retraite
[JOAN:] Get out! They're waiting!
Get out!
They're waiting! Oh!
English are waiting for you!
[KING CHARLES VII:] Every time I look at you
I don't understand
Why you let the things
you did get so out of hand
You'd have managed better
if you'd follow what I planned
Oh
[FOLLOWERS:] Always hoped that I'd be of service.
Knew that I would earn it if I tried.
If I tried
Then when we retire, we can chant of Orléans,
So they'll still talk about us
et la France.
[JOAN:] Will no one pray with me?
Soldiers?
Priests?
Frenchmen?
Will none of you burn with me?
Soldiers?
Priests?
Frenchmen?
[JOAN:] I only wish to say,
If there’s a way,
Keep the flames away from me,
For I am weaker than this torment.
Feel it burn me,
I have changed.
Once I heard voices, clear and sparkling.
Then, I was chosen.
Now, I’m trapped and poisoned.
Listen, surely I've met
Heaven's expectations,
Fought one long year,
seemed like twenty.
Has Jesus asked as much
from any other soul?
But if I burn,
See my path through
and keep my standard true,
Let them mock me,
scorn me, chain me,
stake me to the flames.
I want to know,
I want to know, dear Jesus,
Want to know,
I want to know, good Jesus,
Want to see,
I want to see, dear Saints,
Why I must burn.
Will my name shine brighter
than it ever has before?
Will all the hearts I moved
beat same drum evermore?
I need to know,
I need to know, dear Jesus,
Need to know,
I need to know, good Jesus,
Need to see,
I need to see, dear Saints,
I need to see, good Saints,
If I am ash
what will then be my crown?
Need to know,
I need to know, dear Jesus,
I need to know,
I need to know, good Jesus,
I need to know, my God,
Why must I burn?
Oh,
why must I burn?
Can you tell me now
my dust won't be forgotten?
Show me just a fragment
of your grand celestial plane.
Show me there's a reason
for my toils and pain.
You've chosen me for grilling
and tasked Rouen for embers.
Alright,
I'll burn!
Oh oh oh Just
Just watch me burn!
See
See how I burn!
Oh oh oh oh
Yeah
See how I burn!
Back then I was chosen,
Now, I'm trapped and poisoned.
After all,
I've tried for one year,
seems like always.
Angel Michael, for The Throne,
your white standard I've flown
In Rouen's fiery dawn,
I'll burn for Christ,
alone.
Heaven, your purpose is vast,
But in you, my trust is cast.
I'll wear your garb,
accept my past.
Take me to your stake,
Rouen.
Burn me, light me,
End me.
Take me, now!
Before my heart gives up.
[CAUCHON:] We've been sitting on
the fence for far too long
[D'ESTIVET:] Why let her upset us?
Cauchon, let her be
All those imbeciles will see
She really doesn't matter
[CAUCHON:] Joan is important,
We've let her go her way before.
And while she starts the revolution
We theorize and chatter
[D'ESTIVET:] He's just another
scripture-thumping hack from Lorraine
[CAUCHON:] The difference is they call her a Saint
This difference frightens me!
What about the Church?
When they see a new Maid crowned,
Do you think they'll stand around
Cheering and applauding?
What about our cardinals?
If they see we've lost our nerve
Don't you think that they deserve
Something less challenging?
[D'ESTIVET:] But followers got what they want
They think so anyway
If she's what they want
Why take their toy away?
She's a craze
[CAUCHON:] Put yourself in my place
I can hardly step aside
Cannot let my hands be tied
I am canon law and order
What about our priesthood?
Don't you see that we could fall
If we are to last at all?
We cannot be divided
[D'ESTIVET:] Then say so to the Clerics
But don't rely on subtlety
Let English scare them or they won't see
[CAUCHON:] Then we are decided?
[D'ESTIVET:] Then we are decided.
[CHARLES VII:] Now if I help you,
it matters that you see
These sordid kind of things
are coming hard to me
It's taken me some time
to work out what to do
I weighed the whole thing out
before I came to you
I have no thought at all about my own reward
I really didn't come here of my own accord
Just don't say I'm
Damned for all time!
I came because I had to
I'm the one who saw
Joan can't control it like she did before
And furthermore
I know that Joan thinks so too
Joan wouldn't mind that I was here with you
I have no thought at all about my own reward
I really didn't come here of my own accord
Just don't say I'm
Damned for all time!
Burgundians, you're friends, worldly men and wise
Cauchon, my friend I know you sympathize
Why are we the prophets?
Why are we the ones?
We see the sad solution
Know what must be done
I have no thought at all about my own reward
I really didn't come here of my own accord
Just don't say I'm
Damned
For all time!
[BURGUNDIANS:] Cut the protesting
Forget the excuses
We want information
Get up off the floor
[CAUCHON:] We have the papers
We need to arrest her
You know her movements
We know the canon law
[BURGUNDIANS:] Your help in this matter
won't go unrewarded
[CAUCHON:] We'll pay you in silver cash on the nail
We just need to know
where the soldiers can find her
[BURGUNDIANS:] With no armies around her
Then we can't fail
[CHARLES VII:] I don't want your blood money
[CAUCHON:] That doesn't matter,
our expenses are good
[CHARLES VII:] I don't need your blood money
[BURGUNDIANS:] But you might as well take it
We think that you should
[CAUCHON:] Think of the things
you can do with that money
Choose any charity, give to the poor
We've noted your motives
We've noted your feelings
[CAUCHON:] This isn't blood money, it's a...
[BURGUNDIANS:] A fee.
[CAUCHON:] A fee, nothing more
[CHARLES VII:] On Tuesday morning
You'll find her where you want her
Far from her army
tired, locked out of gates
(MUMBLES)
of Compiégne
[BURGUNDIANS:] Well done Sire
Good old Charles
[JOAN:] Sire,
must you betray me...
before I win Paris?
(FLY BUZZING)
[FOLLOWERS:] What's the buzz
Tell me what's happening
What's the buzz
What's happening?
Tell me what's a-happening
What's the buzz
Hang on, Joan
We're gonna fight for you
[JOAN:] Put away your sword
Don't you know that it's all over?
It was nice, but now it's gone
Why are you obsessed with fighting?
Stick to treaties from now on
(CROWD CHATTERING)
(TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
[FOLLOWERS:] Tell me, Joan,
how you feel tonight
Do you plan to put up a fight?
Do you feel that you've had the breaks?
What would you say were your big mistakes?
Do you think that you may retire?
Did you think you would get much higher?
How do you view your coming trial?
Have your men proved it's all worthwhile?
Come with us - don't be seditious
You'll just love Rouen's courthouse
You'll just love seeing Cauchon
You'll just burn in the marketplace
Come on, Joan, this is not like you
Let us know what you're gonna do
You know what your supporters feel
You'll escape in the final reel
Tell me, Joan, how you feel tonight
Do you plan to put up a fight?
Do you feel that you had the breaks?
What would you say were your big mistakes?
Come with us - don't be seditious
You'll just love Rouen's courthouse
You'll just love seeing Cauchon
You'll just burn in the market place
Now we have her, now we've got her
Now we have her now
We have got her now
[CAUCHON:] Jeanne, you must realize
The serious charges facing you
You say you hear voices of saints
in all your posts
Well, is it true?
That's what you say
You say that I hear
There you have it, gentlemen
What more evidence do we seek?
Charles, thank you for the Maid
Stay a while and you'll see it smoke!
[FOLLOWERS:] Now we have her, now we've got her
Now we have her, now we've got her
Take her to Rouen, take her to Rouen!
[CHURCH ACTOR ONE:] Most Reverend Cauchon
the courtroom waits your grace
The theologians
and clerics are here for the case
[CAUCHON:]Ah gentlemen
you know our task in Rouen
We've not much time
and big ask from Paris, London, Rome
[FOLLOWERS:] Vive la Vierge Jeanne! Long live Supermaiden!
Vive la Pucelle! Our Savioress!
Vive la Vierge Jeanne! Long live Supermaiden!
[D'ESTIVET:] Listen to that clamor
of peasants in the street
A maid lifts up a banner
and they fall at her feet
[COURTROOM FOLLOWERS:] She is dangerous!
[FOLLOWERS:] Joan of Arc, Our Savioress!
[FOLLOWERS:] Tell us that you are
who we say that you are
[CHURCH ACTOR TWO:] The Maid is in the tower
she will appear in court
[CHURCH ACTOR THREE:] A rabble-rousing mission
we are tasked to abort
[COURTROOM FOLLOWERS:] She is dangerous!
[FOLLOWERS:] Joan of Arc,
Our Savioress!
[COURTROOM FOLLOWERS:] She is dangerous!
[CHURCH ACTOR TWO:] Your Excellency, she steps right outside our yard
[CHURCH ACTOR THREE:] Most Reverend Cauchon, let in her English vanguard
[CAUCHON:] No, wait!
We need a more lasting solution
to any presumed plebiscite
[D'ESTIVET:] What then to do about this Joan of Arc?
Peasant supermaid, heroine of fools.
[CHURCH ACTOR THREE:] No riots, no armies,
no credo, no sainting
[CAUCHON:] One thing I'll say —- this Joan's not that bad
[D'ESTIVET:] We dare not leave her to her own devices,
Her misguided armies will soon get out of hand.
[COURTROOM FOLLOWERS:] But how can we stop her?
Her glamour increases,
She’s capturing cities;
she's topping the trends.
[CAUCHON:] I see bad things arising
The crowd-crowned queen,
the Word Order would ban
I see blood and rebranding
Our jobs outsourced because of one girl
Blood and rebranding because of one girl
[COURTROOM:] Because, because, because of one girl
[CAUCHON:] Our elimination because of one girl
[COURTROOM:] Because, because, because of one
Cause of one, cause of one girl
[CHURCH ACTOR THREE:] What then to do about this Joan mania?
[D'ESTIVET:] Now how do we deal
with a shepherdess queen?
[CHURCH ACTOR TWO:] Where do we start
with a Maiden bigger
[CHURCH ACTOR THREE:] Than even Charles was
when Charles was still the VI-th?
[CAUCHON:] Fools, you have no perception!
The stakes we are gambling
are frighteningly high!
We must burn her completely,
Like Charles VI before her,
this Joan of Arc must die.
For the sake of our Mother,
Catholic Church, no relics.
[COURTROOM FOLLOWERS:] Must die, must burn, this Joan must burn.
[CAUCHON:] Like Charles before Charles, this Joan has to die.
[COURTROOM FOLLOWERS:] We must burn her completely, this Maiden must burn to thin dust!
She must burn completely,
no proof of her being to everlast!
[JOAN:]
Christ, forgive the English and Rouen.
For they don't know what they're doing.
Jesus, Jesus,
why have you forgotten me?
Lord,
into your hand,
I commend my spirit.
[JESUS:] Try not to get worried
Try not to turn onto
Problems that upset you
Don't you know everything's all right?
Yes, everything's fine
And we want you to sleep well tonight
Let the world turn without you tonight
If we try, we'll get by
so forget all about us tonight
[FOLLOWERS:] Everything's all right, yes
Everything's all right, yes
[JESUS:] Sleep and I shall soothe you
Calm you and anoint you
Myrrh for your hot forehead
Then you'll feel everything's all right
Yes, everything's fine
And it's cool and the ointment's sweet
For the fire in your head and feet
Close your eyes, close your eyes
Relax, think of light tonight
[FOLLOWERS:] Everything's all right, yes
Everything's all right, yes
[KING CHARLES VII:] Hey, Christ
Your fine ointment, brand-new and exquisite
Should have been saved for a king
Why has it been wasted?
We could have raised maybe
300 silver pieces or more
People who are important
People who are of might
They matter more than
a paysanne's skin!
[JESUS:] Try not to get worried
Try not to turn onto
Problems that upset you
[JESUS:] Don't you know everything's all right?
[FOLLOWERS:] All right, yes
Everything's all right, yes
[JOAN:] Surely you're not saying
We have been elected
To lead kings against their will?
There will be mad kings
always in power
Look at the good things you've got!
Think while you still have France
Move while you still rule France
You'll be lost and you'll be sad
without a kingdom.
[JESUS:] Sleep and I shall soothe you
Calm you and anoint you
Myrrh for your hot forehead
Then you'll feel everything's all right, yes
Everything's fine
And it's cool and the ointment's sweet
For the fire in your head and feet
Close your eyes
Close your eyes and relax
Think of light
Tonight
[FOLLOWERS:] Close your eyes, close your eyes and relax
Think of light
[JESUS:] Close your eyes, close your eyes and relax
[FOLLOWERS:] Everything's all right, yes
[FOLLOWERS:] Everything's a light, yes
Close your eyes, close your eyes and relax
Everything's all light, yes
Everything's PURE LIGHT, yes
[KING CHARLES VII:] It seems to me a strange thing
Mystifying
That a Christ like you bestows his light
On a lowly paysanne like her
[LA HIRE] Hey, cool it, king.
[KING CHARLES VII:] Yes, I can understand that
She is a hero
But to let her hear you and your saints
That's hardly in your line
It's not that I object to her toils
But she doesn't fit in well
with what your Church teaches
It doesn't help us if the Church is inconsistent
The English only need a small excuse
To make all world theirs
[JESUS CHRIST:] Who are you to criticize her?
Who are you to despise her?
Leave her, leave her
Let her be now
She's with me now
If your slate is clean
then you can throw stones
If your slate is not, then leave her alone!
[FOLLOWERS:] Hey, Jesus, what do we say?
-Hey, Jesus, what do we say?
-(CLAMORING)
[JESUS CHRIST:] I'm amazed that you influencers
Can be so shallow, thick and slow
There is not a soul among you
who knows or cares where I come or go
[FOLLOWERS:] No, you're wrong
You're very wrong
No, you're wrong
How can you say that?
[JESUS CHRIST:] Not one.
[JESUS CHRIST:] Not one of you!
[FOLLOWERS:] What's the buzz
Tell me what's a-happening
What's the buzz
[JESUS CHRIST:] Why should you want to know?
Don't you mind about the future
Don't you try to think ahead
Save tomorrow for tomorrow
Think about today instead
[FOLLOWERS:] What's the buzz
Tell me what's a-happening
[JESUS CHRIST:] I could give you facts and figures
[FOLLOWERS:] What's the buzz
Tell me what's a-happening
[JESUS CHRIST:] Even give you plans and forecasts
[FOLLOWERS:] When do we ride to Paris?
When do we ride to Paris?
[JESUS CHRIST:] Even tell you where I'm going
[FOLLOWERS:] When do we ride to Paris?
When do we ride to Berlin?
When do we ride to London?
When do we ride to New York?
When do we ride to Mars?
[JESUS CHRIST:] Why should you want to know?
Why are you obsessed with fighting
Times and fates you can't defy?
If you knew the path we're riding
You'd understand it less than I
[FOLLOWERS:] What's the buzz
Tell me what's a-happening
What's the buzz
[JOAN:] Let me try to carry your cross for a bit
Let me try to carry your cross for a bit
Let me try to carry the cross
Let me try, let me try
To carry the cross
Let me try to carry your cross for a bit
[JESUS CHRIST:] Joan, mmm, that is good
While you chatter through your threads
Where and when and who and how
She alone is trying to give me
What I need right here and now
[FOLLOWERS:] What's the buzz
Tell me what's a-happening
What's the buzz
[NAPOLEON:] Who is
This ghostly maid
appearing
in my presence?
Who is this spectral form?
[FOLLOWER:] It's Joan of Arc,
Queen of France.
[NAPOLEON:] Ah.
So this is Joan of Arc.
I've read about your spark.
You look so small.
Unfit for a war.
I've heard your tale of woes,
But are you she?
The Armored Savioress?
[JOAN:] Your words, not mine.
[NAPOLEON:] What do
you mean by that?
That is not proper reply
Je suis l'Empereur
du Monde, shepherd
Called Queen of the French
How can someone in your state
Be so cool about her fate?
Perplexing circumstance,
this silent queen of France.
Since you fought for The Cross
I am surely not your boss
You're Church's face!
(SMIRKS)
You're Pope's case!
[FOLLOWERS:] Hey Joan, Hey Joan
Joan of Arc
Hey Joan, brave heart
your spark will start
please make it clear
You led men before,
Why are you here?
Joan,
I am extatic...
(SINGING)  To meet you face-to-face
You got signs of sainthood
all around your case
-Leading armies
-Ooh.
Hearing voices from on-high
(ALL GASP)
And some claim you're God-sent
-(GASPS)
-Mmm.
-Huh?
THE POPE: (SINGING)
that I must canonize.
So
So, you are the Maid
you're the Church's SuperMaid
Operate the change of fate;
anoint yourself a saint
Perform this small feat
make all skeptics retreat
Come on, Supermaiden
Joan, you can't conceive
the stir you've made in Rome
You're on everyone's lips,
from pauper to the dome
Oh
What a tale if it turns out false, my dear
But I believe
you could sway the critics, have no fear
So, you are the Maid,
you're Church's SuperMaid.
Show to me you're Heaven's tool;
walk unburned through fiery fuel
-If you pass through the flame,
-CROWD: Whoo!
-holy I will make your name
Come on, Maid of Orléans
I ask you as I would of any saint-to-be
What gift from God was placed on you
where all the world can see?
Oh-oh-oh
I am waiting
as the Church's guiding hand
Awaiting proof that you're apart
from those in the normy band
So, if you are the Maid
the proclaimed Saint Joan
Fill the github with your deeds
heal world hunger and all needs
Or are tales all gone wrong?
Joan, why make us wait so long?
Oh! Come on, you Supermaiden
(SINGING)  Hey! Doesn't
Church Triumphant scare you, Joan?
Oh, Venerable Joan of Arc?
You're a trademark, not a saint.
Proof is what we want, not quaint.
(SINGS)  Keep her away,
Next audience: next century!
Speak no more, Joan of,
Silence, Joan of,
Quiet, you Venerable Blessed Saint Joan of Arc!
THE POPE: Leave our records!
Your standard leads nowhere, Joan,
Erase her from our archives!
[NAPOLEON:] And so the Queen
Is once again my guest
And why is this?
Was The Pope unimpressed?
[CAUCHON:] We turn to history
To seal our judgement
We have no way
To pain her after death
We need her totally forgotten
It's all you have to do
We need her erased from history
[NAPOLEON:] Talk to me, Joan of Arc
You have been brought here
Manacled, burned, by your own people.
Do you have the first idea
why you deserved it?
[NAPOLEON:] Listen Savioress of France,
Where are your saved?
Look at me
Am I saved?
[JOAN:] I have no savings
In the world, I'm through.
[FOLLOWERS:] Talk to me, Joan of Arc
[JOAN:] There may be something saved for me somewhere.
If you only knew.
[NAPOLEON:] Then you are a savioress?
[JOAN:] It's you who say I am
I look for truth and find that I get grilled
[NAPOLEON:] And what is truth?
Is truth unchanging law?
We both have truths
Are mine the same as yours?
[FOLLOWERS:] Forget of her! Erase her deeds!
[NAPOLEON:] What do you mean? You'd forget your savioress?
[FOLLOWERS:] We have no savior but our own selves!
[NAPOLEON:] She's done no wrong.
No, not the slightest thing.
[FOLLOWERS:] We have no savior but our own selves!
Erase her!
[NAPOLEON:] What is this new respect for self?
This looks imported from New Orleans.
Who is this Saint? Why is she different?
You choose bad leaders by the sackful.
[FOLLOWERS:] We need her edited out,
It's all you have to do
We need her erased,
[NAPOLEON:] Talk to me, Joan of Arc
Look at your Joan of Arc
I'll agree she's mad
Ought to be re-trialed
But that is not a reason to erase her
She's a sad, little girl, not a Savior or Christ
Not even a liar, I need a crime!
[FOLLOWERS:] Erase her! Erase her!
(CLAMORING)
Erase her! Erase her!
[NAPOLEON:] Behold a Maiden,
behold your shattered Queen
[FOLLOWERS:] We have no saviour but US!
[NAPOLEON:] You hypocrites,
you hate US more than her
[FOLLOWERS:] We have no king but US!
Erase her!
[NAPOLEON:] I see no reason, I find no evil
This girl is harmless
so why does she upset you?
She's just misguided, thinks she's important
But to keep you vultures happy,
I shall edit her!
[FOLLOWERS:] Erase her! Erase her!
Erase! Erase!
Erase her! Erase her!
[NAPOLEON:] One,
(YELLS)
two,
three,
four,
five,
six,
seven,
eight,
nine,
(PANTS)
(PANTING)
[NAPOLEON:] Where are you from, Jeanne?
What do you want, Jeanne?
Tell me
You've got to be careful
You could be erased soon
Could well be
Why do you not speak
When I hold your history in my hands?
How can you stay quiet?
I don't believe you understand
[JOAN:] You have no power in your hands
Any power you have
comes to you from far beyond.
Everything is fixed, and you can't change it.
[NAPOLEON:] You're a fool, Joan of Arc!
How can I help you?
[FOLLOWERS:] Napoleon, erase her! Erase!
For all posterity
You have a duty to document French virtues
So, erase her!
For all posterity
You'll be demoted, you'll be deported
Erase her!
For all posterity
You have a duty to document French virtue
So erase her!
For all posterity
You'll be demoted, you'll be deported
Erase her!
For all posterity
You have a duty to document French virtue
So erase her!
For all posterity
You'll be demoted, you'll be deported
Erase her!
[NAPOLEON:] Don't let me stop
Your great self-destruction
Be forgotten if you want to
You misguided martyr!
I wash my hands
Of your demolition
Be forgotten if you want to
You innocent soul!
[JESUS CHRIST:] Close your eyes, close your eyes
Look up into
The Light
I know how to lead her.
What to do
How to move her
She's been changed
Yes, really changed
In these past few hundred years
since she is here,
She seems like someone else.
I don't know how to take this
I can see why she moves me
She's a girl
She's just a girl
And I've led so many girl souls before,
In very many ways
She's just one more
Should I bring her down
Should I rise her up?
Should I speak of might
Let my Heavens light?
I bent light come into her
Will she see it inside?
Don't ya think it's rather funny
I should be in this position?
I'm the one
Who's always been
So calm, so cool
A model of God's tool
Running the ageless show
She loves me so
I feel her true
Now she's anew
Her scars erased
Her mission rebased
Now she will see
What she was meant
To be
What her burning
Meant for me
In my eternity
In God's eternity
She trusts me so
I know her so
I guide her
Soul
[roles of: La Hire, Mercenaries]
[MERCENARIES:]
Joan, you know I love you.
Did you see my grin?
I believe in you and Christ,
So lead me to a win.
Joan, you know I love you.
Did you see my grin?
I believe in you and Christ,
So lead me to a win.
Joan, I am with you.
Guide me, guide me, Joan.
Joan, I fight for you.
Lead me, lead me, Joan.
[LA HIRE:]
Joan, what more do you need to convince you,
That you're our Leader and easily as strong
As the English who plunder our homeland,
And who've terrorized the Frenchmen for so long.
[MERCENARIES:]
Joan, I am with you.
Guide me, guide me, Joan.
Joan, I fight for you.
Lead me, lead me, Joan.
Joan, you know I love you.
Did you see my grin?
I believe in you and Christ,
So lead me to a win.
Joan, I am with you.
Guide me, guide me, Joan.
Joan, I fight for you.
Lead me, lead me, Joan.
[LA HIRE:]
There must be legions upon legions
Screaming love and blood for you.
[MERCENARIES:]
Love! Love! Blood! Love!
[LA HIRE:]
And every man of all these legions
Would do whatever you ask him to.
[MERCENARIES:]
Anything you ask me to!
[LA HIRE:]
Keep them yelling their devotion,
But add a touch of hate of English band.
You will rise a greater standard,
We will win ourselves a land.
You'll get the might and the light
For ever and ever and ever
You'll get the might and light,
you'll get to be a saint
For ever and ever and ever
Forever Amen! Amen! Amen!
[roles of: Joan of Arc]
[JOAN OF ARC:]
Neither you, la Hire, nor the legions,
Nor the English, nor the Church,
Nor the UN, nor my saved souls,
Nor the priests, nor Google search,
Nor redeemed Orléans itself
Understand what might is,
Understand what light is,
Understand at all,
Understand at all.
If you knew all that I knew, my poor France,
You'd see the truth, but you close your eyes.
But you close your eyes.
While you crave, your troubles are many, poor France.
To conquer greed, you only have to give.
You only have to give.
(CHATTERING)
CHORUS:  Roll on up, old faire Rouen
Come on in, old faire Rouen
Sunday, here we go again
Live in me, old faire Rouen
Here you live, old faire Rouen
Here you breathe, old faire Rouen
While Joan's saga still survives
You at least are still alive
I got things you won't believe
Name your pleasure, I will sell
ALL:  I can fix your wildest needs
I got heaven, I got hell
CHORUS:  Roll on up for my price is down
Come on in for the best in town
Take your pick of the finest wine
Lay your bets on this bird of mine
What you see is what you get
No one's been disappointed yet
Don't be scared, give me a try
There is nothing you can't buy
CHORUS:  Name your price, I got everything
Hurry, it's all going fast
Borrow cash on the finest terms
Hurry now while stocks still last
(ALL CHATTERING)
Roll on up, old faire Rouen
Come on in, old faire Rouen
Sunday, here we go again
Live in me, old faire Rouen
Here you live, old faire Rouen
Here you breathe, old faire Rouen
While Joan's saga still survives
You at least are still alive
I got things you won't believe
Name your pleasure, I will sell
(WOMEN SCREAMING)
(SINGING)  My death place should be
A house of good deeds
-(CLAMORING)
-(WOMAN SCREAMS)
But you have made it
A den of thieves
Rouen, Rouen.
You grilled me through.
For how many centuries
Have you sold my ashes?
(SINGING)  My time
Is almost through
Little left to do
After all
I've tried for centuries
Almost 6
Seems like always
See my time, I can hardly stop
See my face, it is hardly fair
I believe you can make me whole
See my votes, I need much more
MAN:  See my likes, I have too few
Fix the press, for my campaign
I believe you can make me well
See my account, I'm a poor, poor man
ALL:  Will you touch,
will you mend me, Joan?
Won't you touch, will you heal me, Joan?
Will you kiss, you can cure me, Joan
Won't you give, won't you pay me, Joan?
See my time, I can hardly stop
See my face, it is hardly fair
I believe you can make me whole
See my votes, I need much more
See my belly, I'm too fat
See my legs, I can hardly stand
I believe you can give me luck
See my account, I'm a poor, poor man
Will you touch, will you heal me, Joan?
Won't you touch, will you cuddle me, Joan?
Will you kiss, you can like me, Joan
Won't you give, won't you pay me, Joan?
See my time, I can hardly stop
See my face, it is hardly fair
I believe you can make me whole
See my votes, I need much more
See my belly, I'm too fat
See my time, I can hardly stop
I believe you can give me luck
See my account, I'm a poor, poor man
Will you touch, will you mend me, Joan?
Won't you touch, will you heal me, Joan?
Will you kiss, you can heal me, Joan
Won't you give, won't you pay me, Joan?
See my time, I can hardly stop
See my face, it is hardly fair
I believe you can give me luck
See my votes, I need much more
See my belly, I'm too fat
JOAN: There's too many of you!
I believe you can give me luck
JOAN: Don't push me!
Will you touch, will you mend me, Joan?
There's too little of me.
Will you kiss, you can like me, Joan
Don't crowd me!
See my time, I can hardly stop
Leave me alone!
See my votes, I need much more
MAN: Please, Joan!
WOMAN: Touch me, Joan!
[TODAY]
[JESUS CHRIST:] I've been waiting to see you.
You've been burning to see me,
but it shouldn't be like this.
You have over-performed,
Ready for Joan of Arc Romee, anew?
You are my only hope.
Papalis Infallibilitas too much.
Now for the first time,
I think The Pope was wrong.
Awake him ex cathedra,
Make his judgement pro tempore.
Joan, could we start la nouvelle guerre spirituelle?
[THE POPE:] I think you've made your point now.
You've even gone a bit too far to get the message home.
Before it gets too far,
We ought to call a vote,
Joan, could we start la nouvelle guerre spirituelle?
I've been waiting to see you.
You've been burning to see me,
but it shouldn't be like this.
You have over-performed,
Ready to be anew Joan of Arc Romee?
You are my only hope.
I think you've made your point now.
You've even gone a bit too far
to get the message home.
Before it gets too far,
We ought to call a vote,
Joan could we together start again la guerre?
Could we start la nouvelle guerre spirituelle? (1/5)
Could we start la nouvelle guerre spirituelle? (2/5)
Could we start la nouvelle guerre spirituelle? (3/5)
Could we start la nouvelle guerre spirituelle? (4/5)
[JESUS CHRIST:] Joan, could we start la nouvelle guerre spirituelle?
[TODAY]
[NAPOLEON:] Every time I look at you,
I don't understand
Why you let the things
you did get so out of hand
You'd have managed better
if I'd had you planned
Now why'd you choose
such a backward time in such a strange land?
If you'd come today
you could have reached the whole nation
France in 15th cent had no mass communication
[FOLLOWERS:] Don't you get me wrong
[NAPOLEON:] Don't you get me wrong
[FOLLOWERS:] Don't you get me wrong now
[FOLLOWERS:] Don't you get me wrong
[NAPOLEON:] Don't you get me wrong
[FOLLOWERS:] Don't you get me wrong now
[FOLLOWERS:] Only wanna know
[NAPOLEON:] Only wanna know
[FOLLOWERS:] Only wanna know now
[FOLLOWERS:] Only wanna know
[NAPOLEON:] Only wanna know
I only wanna know
[FOLLOWERS:] Joan of Arc
Joan of Arc
Who are you?
Why were you sacrificed?
Joan of Arc
Who are you?
Why were you sacrificed?
Joan of Arc
SuperMaid
Do you think you're what we say you are?
Joan of Arc
SuperMaiden
Do you think you're what we say you are?
[NAPOLEON:] Tell me
What you think about your friends at the top
Now who'd you think besides yourself
was the pick of the crop?
Buddha, was he where it's at?
Is he where you are?
Was Jesus truly Christ,
or was his mind subpar?
Did you mean to burn like that?
Was that a mistake,
Or did you know your story
would spawn record fakers?
[FOLLOWERS:] Don't you get me wrong
[NAPOLEON:] Don't you get me wrong
[FOLLOWERS:] Don't you get me wrong now
[FOLLOWERS:] Don't you get me wrong
[NAPOLEON:] Don't you get me wrong
[FOLLOWERS:] Don't you get me wrong now
[FOLLOWERS:] Only wanna know
[NAPOLEON:] Only wanna know
[FOLLOWERS:] Only wanna know now
[FOLLOWERS:] Only wanna know
[NAPOLEON:] Only wanna know
[FOLLOWERS:] Only wanna know now
I only wanna know
Joan of Arc
Who are you?
Why were you sacrificed?
Joan of Arc
Who are you?
Why were you sacrificed?
[FOLLOWERS:] Joan of Arc, SuperMaid
[NAPOLEON:] Jeanne
[FOLLOWERS:] I only wanna know
[NAPOLEON:] Do you think you're what they say you are?
[FOLLOWERS:] Tell me, tell me, tell me, tell me
[NAPOLEON:] Joan of Arc, SuperMaid
Don't you get me wrong
I only wanna know
[FOLLOWERS:] Joan of Arc, I only wanna know
Jeanne
I only wanna know
[FOLLOWERS:] Joan of Arc, I only wanna know
[NAPOLEON:] Tell me, tell me, tell me, tell me
[FOLLOWERS:] Tell me, tell me
[NAPOLEON:] Don't you get me wrong
I only wanna know
Come on
[FOLLOWERS:] Jeanne
[NAPOLEON:] Jeanne
Jeanne
[FOLLOWERS:] Only wanna know, Jeanne
[FOLLOWERS:] Only wanna know
[NAPOLEON:] I only wanna know
[NAPOLEON:] Tell me, tell me, tell me, tell me
Joan of Arc, SuperMaid
Don't you get me wrong,
I only wanna know
[NAPOLEON:] Come on, Jeanne
[FOLLOWERS:] Joan of Arc
Jeanne
I only wanna know
Tell me
Tell me, tell me, tell me
[FOLLOWERS:] I think I've seen you somewhere
I remember.
You were with that maid they took away
I recognize your face
[CHURCHMAN:] You've got the wrong man, people
I don't know her
And I wasn't where she was
Never near the place
[FOLLOWERS:] That's strange for I am sure
I saw you with her
You were right by her side
and yet you denied
[CHURCHMAN:] I tell you, I was never, ever with her
[FOLLOWERS:] But I saw you, too. He looked just like you.
[CHURCHMAN:] I don't know that Maid!
[JESUS CHRIST:] Churchman,
Don't you know what you have said?
You've gone and cut Christ dead
[CHURCHMAN:] I had to do it
Don't you see?
Or else they'd go for me
[JESUS CHRIST:] It's what she told you
you would do
Do you wonder
how she knew?
[FOLLOWER:] My God, I saw her
she looked three-quarters dead
and she was so bad, I had to turn my head
You poisoned her
and she was almost broken
And I know who everybody's gonna blame
I don't believe she knows I acted for our good
I'd save her all this suffering if I could
Don't believe our good
And I'd save her if I could
[POLITICIANS:] Cut the confessions, forget the excuses
I don't understand why
you're filled with remorse
All that you've said
has come true with a vengeance
Her followers turned against her
You backed the right horse
What you have done
will be the saving of everyone
You'll be remembered forever for this
And not only that
You've been paid for your efforts
Pretty good wages for one little girl
[FOLLOWER:] Joan, I know you can't hear me
But I only did what your mission needed me to
Joan, I'd sell out the nation
For I have been saddled
with the murder of you
I have been spattered with innocent blood
I shall be dragged
through the slime and the mud
I have been spattered with innocent blood
I shall be dragged
through the slime and the slime and the
Slime and the mud
I
Don't know how to thank her
I don't know why she made me lead
She's a girl
She's just a girl
She is not a Christ
She's just the same
As any other celebrity
She scares me so
While she's scattered ashes
Will she let me free?
Will she forgive
Will she forgive me too?
Does she still care for her Followers?
My mind is
It's in darkness
God.
God, I'm sick!
I've been used!
And you knew all the time!
God! God, I will never know
why you chose me
for your crime!
For your bloody crime!
You have crowned me!
Crowned me!
Crowned me! Elevated me!
Crowned me, Joan!
[FOLLOWERS:] So long, Follower
Poor old Follower
So long, Follower